I wanted to ask you uh so regardless of the fact
that they're saying that you know Venezuela is
sitting on the largest oil deposits in the
world 300 something plus billion barrels
more than Saudis 267 doesn't matter it's how you
analyzed it it's for other reasons I think it's
for other reasons and look at it this way too the
United States literally cannot invade Venezuela
why because Venezuela is the size of Germany,
France, and Austria combined. And it's almost
entirely jungle. There's not an army in the world
big enough to invade and occupy and run Venezuela.
And so I think what we're going to see is
continued pressure on the Venezuelan government,
whether it continues to be this government or it
becomes a puppet government of the United States.
continued pressure for oil um concessions, but
there's not going to be an American occupation.
It wouldn't make any kind of sense. Uh John. Um
the other thing that ran to my mind when this
whole thing unfolded was um how for decades
when it came to Central and South America
starting from the 50s through the 80s um regime
change in that part of the world relied on slow,
covert CIA operations designed to look like
organic popular uprisings. Whereas Trump this
time dispensed with that entire playbook straight
in. Oh my god. He achieved everything in a matter,
you know, operationally in a matter of hours
with what previously took months and plausible
deniability following, you know. So given that
context, how luckily is it that Maduro's arrest
could have could only have happened uh with
an inside job, someone from his inner circle
tipping tipping them off or facilitating
access? 100% that's what happened. Okay.
100% that's exactly what happened. As soon as the
US put a bounty of $50 million on Maduro's head,
you know that people in his immediate inner
circle lined up to volunteer to rat him out
and turn him over to the US government.
Listen, I can tell you Suzy with firsthand
knowledge Uhhuh. that when we put a bounty on
someone, we pay the bounty. Mhm. We pay it.
And I know because I have gone to meetings with
$10 million in two giant gym gym bags full of
cash to pay off the bounty. I can tell you that
we've paid bounties with gold, with diamonds,
with dollars, with land. However you want to
take payment, we're happy to make the payment.
And so as soon as we offered $50 million, we
only offered 20 million for Osama bin Laden,
$50 million, somebody turned him in. Yeah. And I
would I would go so far to say, and this is just
an educated guess based on my own experience. I
don't have any inside information. I would say
there were multiple rats. Not just somebody in
Maduro's inner circle, but at least one person
in the military as well. at least one person in
the military. The military never fought back.
There were no US casualties in this operation.
None. None. The 80. And at the same time,
the Delta forces, they killed 80 people, including
35 Cubans. There were no American casualties. So,
how does how do I know that there was this rat?
Well, number one, the government said that there
was a rat. The the American government said that
there was a rat. But number two, and I'll give
there are three. Number two, in August, Maduro's
personal pilot went public and said that the CIA
had approached him. The CIA had offered him
$50 million so that when Maduro were to get
on the plane to run to Cuba or Russia or Spain
or wherever he was going to run, the pilot would
land the plane instead in Florida so the FBI could
just grab him off the plane. And and number three,
we know that Maduro was changing the locations
where he was sleeping every single night,
just like Saddam Hussein did. Um, so he was
not sleeping in the same bed two nights in a
row. Well, the Delta forces knew EXACTLY where
he was sleeping and they literally physically
pulled him out of the bed. So that just spells
informant. Yeah. But um regarding the bounty,
John, so from where I sit in the Eastern
Mediterranean, there's a striking irony in
watching the Democrats go crazy and denounce the
legality of Maduro's capture when it's the Biden
administration that itself placed the bounty, the
reward on him back in January '25 for 25 million
with Trump bumping it up to 50 million later on in
August '25. So it's it which is an unprecedented
bounty for a head of state and that should be
noted just so Democrats don't yeah, for people
to know... Suzy I have I have to tell you a story
appropo of this of this comment that you just
made. My two oldest sons were in love with fake
wrestling WWE Smackdown you know whatever. And so
I got tickets to a World Wrestling Entertainment
uh show at Madison Square Garden in New York and I
took them. They were like 8 and 5 or or 9 and 6 at
the time. And we're watching these grown men smash
each other against the floor and break chairs over
each other's backs. And I said to my oldest son,
I said, "I don't think I understand which one is
the good guy." And he said, "Well, that's just it,
Dad. There is no good guy. That's the situation
that we find ourselves in today. You look at
Trump, Trump put a $50 million bounty on Maduro.
You look at the Democrats, they put a $25 million
bounty on Maduro. There is no good guy in this
situation. The Democrats are just as guilty as the
Republicans in being cowboys who want to invade
and occupy any country whose leader does not do
exactly as he or she is told. So there is no good
guy in the Democratic party. And something else.